♪♪
[ David Bowie's "Cat People
(Putting Out Fire)" plays ]
♪♪
-♪ See these eyes of green ♪
[ Sirens wailing ]
♪ I can stare
for a thousand years ♪
♪ Colder than the moon ♪
♪ Well. it's been so long ♪
♪ And I've been
putting out fire ♪
[ Thudding ]
♪ With gasoline ♪
♪♪
♪ See these eyes of red ♪
♪ Red like jungle
burning bright ♪
♪ Those who feel me near ♪
♪ Pull the blinds
and change their mind ♪
♪ It's been so long ♪
♪ Well. it's been so long ♪
♪ I've been putting out fire
with gasoline ♪
♪ Putting out fire ♪
[ Tires screeching ]
♪♪
♪ See these tears of blue ♪
♪ An ageless heart
that can never mend ♪
♪ Tears can never dry ♪
♪ A judgment made ♪
♪ Can never bend ♪
[ Engine starts ]
♪ See these eyes so green ♪
♪ I can stare
for a thousand years ♪
♪ Just be still with me ♪
♪ You wouldn't believe
what I've been through ♪
♪ Well. it's been so long ♪
♪ It's been so long ♪
♪ And I've been putting out fire
with gasoline ♪
♪ Putting out fire ♪
♪ With gasoline ♪
[ Gunshot echoes ]
♪♪
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[ Vehicle door opens. closes ]
♪♪
[ Engine starts. idling ]
[ Engine revs ]
[ Sho-Nuff's "Mix Match Man"
plays ]
♪♪
-♪ 'Cause if you don't know me
well ♪
♪ You had better listen ♪
♪ To the facts about me. baby ♪
[ Horn honks ]
♪ That you better know ♪
♪ I'm not one of you ♪
♪ You're not one of me ♪
♪ And the things I see ♪
♪ You may not see ♪
♪ Like. pick up the beat ♪
♪ And close the hand ♪
♪ Check me out. baby ♪
♪ I'm the Mix Match Man ♪
♪ The Mix Match Man ♪
[ Engine stops. music stops ]
-Found it.
Found it.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[ Pen scratching ]
[ Bell chimes ]
[ Liquid pouring ]
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
[ Engine revs.
tires screeching ]
♪♪
[ Horns honking in distance ]
[ Tires screeching ]
[ Engine revving ]
[ Engine revs. tires screech ]
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
♪♪
[ Bag thuds ]
-[ Exhales deeply ]
♪♪
[ Indistinct conversations.
typewriters clicking ]
[ Telephones ringing ]
-Miller.
[ Door closes ]
[ Indistinct conversations.
typewriter clicking ]
[ No audio ]
[ Typewriter bell chimes ]
[ Bill Withers' "Lovely Day"
plays ]
♪♪
-♪ When I wake up
in the morning. love ♪
♪ And the sunlight hurts
my eyes ♪
♪ And something
without warning. love ♪
♪ Bears heavy on my mind ♪
♪ Then I look at you ♪
♪ And the world's all right
with me ♪
♪ Just one look at you ♪
♪ And I know it's gonna be ♪
♪ A lovely day ♪
-♪ Lovely day. lovely day ♪
♪ Lovely day. lovely day ♪
-♪ A lovely day ♪
-♪ Lovely day. lovely day.
lovely day. lovely day ♪
♪ Lovely day. lovely day.
-♪ When the day
that lies ahead of me ♪
♪ Seems impossible to face ♪
♪ When someone else
instead of me ♪
♪ Always seems to know the way ♪
♪ Then I look at you ♪
♪ And the world's all right
with me ♪
♪ Ah. just want one look
at you ♪
♪ And I know it's gonna be ♪
♪ A lovely day ♪
[ Music fades ]
[ Down-tempo music plays ]
♪♪
-[ Gasps ]
[ Softly ] Yeah.
-Yeah?
-[ Laughing ]
Yeah!
Yes!
[ Laughing ]
Oh!
♪♪
[ Laughs ]
Oh!
♪♪
[ No audio ]
[ Fleetwood Mac's "The Chain"
plays ]
♪♪
-♪ Listen to the wind blow ♪
♪ Watch the sun rise ♪
♪♪
♪ Run in the shadows ♪
♪ Damn your love.
damn your lies ♪
♪♪
♪ And if you don't love me now ♪
♪ You will never love me again ♪
♪ I can still hear you saying ♪
♪ You would never break
the chain ♪
-♪ Never break the chain ♪
♪ And if you don't love me now ♪
-♪ You don't love me now ♪
-♪ You will never love me
again ♪
♪ I can still hear you saying ♪
♪ You would never break
the chain ♪
-♪ Never break the chain ♪
[ Helicopter blades whirring ]
[ No audio ]
♪♪
♪ Listen to the wind blow ♪
♪ Down comes the night ♪
♪♪
♪ Run in the shadows ♪
♪ Damn your love.
damn your lies ♪
♪♪
♪ Break the silence ♪
♪ Damn the dark.
damn the light ♪
♪ And if you don't love me now ♪
♪ You will never love me again ♪
♪ I can still hear you saying ♪
♪ You would never break
the chain ♪
-♪ Never break the chain ♪
♪ And if you don't love me now ♪
-♪ You don't love me now ♪
-♪ You will never love me
again ♪
♪ I can still hear you saying ♪
♪ You would never break
the chain ♪
-♪ Never break the chain ♪
-♪ And if you don't love me
now ♪
-♪ You don't love me now ♪
-♪ You will never love me
again ♪
♪ I can still hear you saying ♪
♪ You would never break
the chain ♪
-♪ Never break the chain ♪
♪♪
[ No audio ]
[ Music builds ]
♪♪
[ Helicopter blades whirring ]
♪ Chains ♪
♪ Keep us together ♪
-♪ Running in the shadows ♪
-♪ Chains ♪
♪ Keep us together ♪
-♪ Running in the shadows ♪
-♪ Chains ♪
♪ Keep us together ♪
-♪ Running in the shadows ♪
-♪ Chains ♪
[ Music fades ]
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
♪♪
-[ Sighs ]
[ Clicks tongue ]
♪♪
[ Machine whirring ]
[ Lighter clicks ]
[ Chair scrapes ]
[ Down-tempo music plays ]
♪♪
[ Hand thudding ]
-I loved you!
♪♪
[ Hand thuds ]
[ Muffled ] I loved you!
[ Sobs ]
I loved you!
♪♪
[ Muffled sobbing ]
I loved you!
♪♪
[ Inhales sharply. groans ]
[ Ring clatters ]
[ Sobs ]
[ Footsteps departing ]
♪♪
[ Knock on door ]
[ Buzzer sounds. lock clicks ]
♪♪
[ Handcuffs clinking ]
-♪ To get off. to get off ♪
♪ To get off. to get off ♪
♪ To get off. to get. get off ♪
♪ Looking through that dress
drive me crazy and makes me ♪
-♪ Get off ♪
♪ Sensuality excites my mind.
it makes me ♪
♪ Get off ♪
-♪ If I were you. I'd get
a good perspective on how to ♪
♪ Get off ♪
-Don't fucking touch me.
-Hey.
-♪ Love me wild ♪
-Ow! Fucker!
-♪ Get off ♪
-♪ Tie me up at your place.
I can love you crazy ♪
♪ In the heat.
you will understand ♪
♪ Danger and excitement.
that's what makes a lady ♪
♪ Find out what she wants
in a man ♪
♪ To get off. to get off ♪
-Let's go.
-♪ To get off. to get off ♪
♪ To get off ♪
-Ow!
-♪ To get off ♪
-gtt
-♪ Ooh-ooh! Ooh-ooh!
Ooh-ooh! Ooh-ooh! ♪
-Fuck you!
Stop!
♪♪
-Yeah!
[ Laughs ]
♪ Get off ♪
-Aah! Aah!
[ Gun cocks ]
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
♪♪
[ Gunshot echoes ]
[ Body thuds ]
-[ Breathing heavily ]
♪♪
[ Casings clattering ]
[ Siren wailing in distance ]
♪♪
[ Vehicle door opens ]
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
♪♪
[ Metal clanks. scraping ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
♪♪
[ Music slows. ends ]
[ Buzzer sounds.
indistinct shouting ]
-[ Smooches ]
[ Shouting continues ]
[ Hand slaps ]
[ Indistinct shouting.
man whistles ]
[ Buzzer sounds ]
[ Sniff 'n' the Tears'
"Driver's Seat" plays ]
[ Club thudding ]
♪♪
-♪ Doing all right ♪
♪ A little jiving
on a Saturday night ♪
♪ And come what may ♪
♪ Gonna dance the day away ♪
♪♪
♪ Jenny was sweet ♪
♪ She always smiled
for the people she'd meet ♪
♪ On trouble and strife ♪
♪ She had another way
of looking at life ♪
♪♪
♪ The news is blue ♪
-♪ The news is blue ♪
-♪ It has its own way
to get to you ♪
-♪ Ooh. ooh ♪
-♪ What can I do? ♪
-♪ I'll never remember
my time with you ♪
♪♪
♪ Pick up your feet ♪
♪ Got to move to the trick
of the beat ♪
♪ There is no elite ♪
♪ Just take your place
in the driver's seat ♪
-♪ Driver's seat ♪
♪ Ooh. ooh ♪
♪ Driver's seat ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
-♪ We're doing all right ♪
-♪ Ooh. ooh ♪
-♪ A little jiving
on a Saturday night ♪
-♪ Yeah ♪
-♪ And come what may ♪
-♪ Ooh. ooh ♪
-♪ Gonna dance the day away ♪
-♪ Yeah ♪
-♪ Driver's seat ♪
-♪ Ooh. ooh ♪
[ Paper crinkling ]
-♪ Yeah ♪
[ Telephone rings ]
-♪ Jenny was sweet ♪
-♪ Ooh. ooh ♪
-♪ There is no elite ♪
[ Music fades ]
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
[ Typewriter clicking ]
♪♪
[ Lighter clicks ]
[ Down-tempo music playing ]
♪♪
♪ You got to see I got to go ♪
[ Door opens. bell chimes ]
♪♪
[ Door closes ]
[ Door opens. bell chimes ]
[ Liquid pouring ]
[ Door closes ]
♪♪
♪ 'Cause you know ♪
♪ That would be a lie ♪
♪ I just can't keep it all
inside ♪
♪ I wasn't trying
to keep you down ♪
♪ But I'd like
to keep you around ♪
♪♪
♪ 'Cause you know ♪
♪ I just can't keep it all
inside ♪
♪♪
♪ I just can't keep it all
inside ♪
♪♪
♪ And you can take me
for a ride ♪
♪♪
♪ But if you want me.
just lay low ♪
♪ And make me stay
when I should go ♪
♪♪
♪ I might not talk.
but still you try ♪
♪ Because it's in me.
we know ♪
♪ And you know ♪
[ Lighter clicks ]
♪ I just can't keep it all
inside ♪
♪♪
♪ I just can't keep it all
inside ♪
♪♪
♪ So you can take me
for a ride ♪
♪♪
♪ But if you want me.
just lay low ♪
♪ And make me stay... ♪
-Hello.
-♪ ...when I should go ♪
♪♪
-Hi.
[ Siren wailing in distance ]
♪♪
[ Down-tempo music plays ]
-[ Laughing ]
[ Horn honks ]
♪♪
[ Keys jingling ]
[ Buzzer sounds ]
♪♪
[ Music slows. continues ]
[ Music builds ]
♪♪
[ Donna Summer's "I Feel Love"
plays ]
♪♪
-♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's so good. it's so good.
it's so good ♪
♪ It's so good. it's so good ♪
♪♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Heaven knows. heaven knows.
heaven knows ♪
♪ Heaven knows. heaven knows ♪
♪♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ I feel love. I feel love.
I feel love ♪
♪ I feel love. I feel love ♪
♪♪
♪ I feel love ♪
[ Music fades ]
[ Down-tempo music plays ]
♪♪
[ Indistinct conversations.
voices echoing ]
♪♪
[ Indistinct conversations.
telephone ringing ]
-♪ ...joy ♪
-♪ Gonna have
a merry Christmas ♪
♪ It'll be the real McCoy ♪
♪ We've got things to prepare ♪
♪ Let there be loving ♪
♪ Let us care ♪
♪ Gonna be a merry Christmas
with magic in the air ♪
-♪ We can meet
under the mistletoe ♪
-♪ Doo-wa. doo-wa. ooh-wa ♪
-♪ And we can always hope
there might be snow. oh. oh ♪
♪ Santa Claus is on his way ♪
♪ So prepare for Christmas Day ♪
[ Music fades ]
♪ Let's have a merry Christmas ♪
[ Down-tempo music plays ]
[ Typewriters clicking ]
♪♪
[ "Hark! The Herald Angels Sing"
playing on piano ]
[ Bell clanging ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
♪♪
[ Ice clattering.
music continues ]
♪♪
-Want to mind your own business?
Huh?
Merry fuckin' Christmas.
♪♪
[ Blades squeaking ]
[ Sirens wailing ]
[ Gunshots echoing ]
[ Down-tempo music plays ]
♪♪
[ Gun thuds. blade squeaking ]
[ Paper crinkling ]
♪♪
[ Music slows. continues ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
♪♪
[ Music builds ]
[ Glass breaks ]
-[ Grunting ]
♪♪
[ Glass breaking ]
[ Screaming ]
♪♪
[ The Ray Conniff Singers'
"Ring Christmas Bells" plays ]
[ Shouting indistinctly ]
♪♪
-♪ Ring. Christmas bells.
merrily ring ♪
♪ Tell all the world
Jesus is king ♪
♪ Ring. Christmas bells.
toll loud and long ♪
♪ Your message sweet
heal and prolong ♪
♪ Come. all you people.
join in the singing ♪
♪ Repeat the story
told by the ringing ♪
♪ Ring. ring. ring. ring ♪
♪ Ring. Christmas bells.
throughout the earth ♪
♪ Tell of the news
of Jesus' birth ♪
-♪ Loudly proclaim
with one accord ♪
♪ The happy tale ♪
♪ Welcome the Lord ♪
-♪ Ring. Christmas bells.
merrily ring ♪
♪ Tell all the world
Jesus is king ♪
-♪ Ring ♪
♪♪
♪ Ring Christmas bells.
merrily ring ♪
♪ Tell all the world
Jesus is king ♪
♪ Loudly proclaim
with one accord ♪
♪ The happy tale ♪
♪ Welcome the Lord ♪
♪ Ring. Christmas bells.
sound far and near ♪
♪ The birthday of Jesus
is here ♪
-♪ Herald the news
to old and young ♪
♪ Tell it to all
in every tongue ♪
♪ Ring. ring. ring. ring ♪
♪ Ring ♪
♪ Ahh ♪
♪♪
[ Music fades. ends ]
[ Insects chirping ]
[ Down-tempo music plays ]
♪♪
[ Dog barking in distance ]
[ No audio ]
♪♪
[ Music builds. continues ]
[ Door closes ]
♪♪
[ Tapping ]
[ Tapping continues ]
♪♪
[ Music builds. slows ]
[ Keys jingling ]
[ Door opens ]
♪♪
[ Birds chirping.
vehicle approaching ]
-Yo.
Fuck off. man.
-[ Grunts ]
-Oh! [ Groaning ]
[ Starbuck's
"Moonlight Feels Right" plays ]
♪♪
[ Bat thudding. man groaning ]
-♪ The wind blew some luck
in my direction ♪
♪ I caught it in my hands
today ♪
♪ I finally made
a tricky French connection ♪
♪ You winked and gave me
your okay ♪
♪ I'll take you on a trip
beside the ocean ♪
♪ And drop the top
at Chesapeake Bay ♪
-[ Whistles ]
[ Fingers snapping ]
-♪ Ain't nothing like
a scattered dose of ocean ♪
♪ The moon will send you
on your way ♪
[ Chuckles ]
♪ Moonlight ♪
♪♪
♪ Feels right ♪
♪ Moonlight ♪
♪♪
♪ Feels right ♪
♪ We'll lay back and observe
the constellations ♪
♪ And watch the moon
smiling bright ♪
♪ I'll play the radio
on Southern stations ♪
♪ 'Cause Southern belles
are hell at night ♪
♪ You say you came to Baltimore
from Ole Miss ♪
♪ A class of '74 gold ring ♪
♪ The eastern moon looks ready
for a wet kiss ♪
♪ To make the tide rise again ♪
[ Chuckles ]
♪ Moonlight ♪
♪♪
♪ Feels right ♪
♪ Moonlight ♪
♪♪
[ Gunshots echoing ]
♪ Feels right ♪
♪♪
-[ Whistles ]
[ Whistles ]
Hey!
♪♪
[ Grunts ]
♪ We'll see the sun come up
on Sunday morning ♪
♪ And watch it fade the moon
away ♪
♪ I guess you know
I'm giving you a warning ♪
♪ 'Cause me and moon
are itching to play ♪
♪ I'll take you on a trip
beside the ocean ♪
♪ And drop the top
at Chesapeake Bay ♪
♪ Ain't nothing like
a scattered dose of ocean ♪
♪ The moon will send you
on your way ♪
[ Chuckles ]
♪ Moonlight ♪
♪♪
[ Music fades ]
♪ Feels right ♪
[ Down-tempo music plays ]
[ Pencil clatters ]
♪♪
[ Blade scraping ]
[ Plastic crinkling ]
♪♪
[ Water splashes ]
[ Keys jingling ]
[ Latch clicks ]
♪♪
-[ Grunting ]
[ Club clattering ]
[ Grunting stops ]
♪♪
[ Vehicle approaching ]
[ Music builds ]
♪♪
[ Keys jingling ]
-Hey.
Whoa.
I'm just playing. man.
[ Down-tempo music plays ]
[ Hinges squeaking ]
♪♪
[ The Moody Blues'
"Nights in White Satin" plays ]
♪♪
-♪ Nights in white satin ♪
♪ Never reaching the end ♪
♪ Letters I've written ♪
[ Lock clicks. buzzer sounds ]
♪ Never meaning to send ♪
♪ Beauty I've always missed ♪
♪ With these eyes before ♪
♪ Just what the truth is ♪
♪ I can't say any more ♪
♪ 'Cause I love you ♪
♪ Yes. I love you ♪
♪ Oh. how I love you ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪♪
♪ Gazing at people ♪
♪ Some hand in hand ♪
♪ Just what I'm going through ♪
♪ They can't understand ♪
♪ Some try to tell me ♪
[ Indistinct shouting ]
♪ Thoughts they cannot defend ♪
♪ Just what you want to be ♪
♪ You will be in the end ♪
♪ And I love you ♪
♪ Yes. I love you ♪
♪ Oh. how I love you ♪
[ Tapping ]
[ Fist thuds ]
-[ Grunts ]
[ Body thuds ]
[ Lock clicks. buzzer sounds ]
♪♪
♪ Nights in white satin ♪
♪ Never reaching the end ♪
♪ Letters I've written ♪
♪ Never meaning to send ♪
[ Alarm blaring ]
♪ Beauty I've always missed ♪
[ Tires screeching.
engine revving ]
♪ 'Cause I love you ♪
[ Gunshot echoes ]
♪ Yes. I love you ♪
♪ Oh. how I love you ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ 'Cause I love you ♪
♪ Yes. I love you ♪
♪ Oh. how I love you ♪
[ Music builds ]
♪♪
[ Music ends ]
[ Explosion echoes.
engine revving ]
[ Insects chirping ]
[ Telephone ringing ]
[ Line ringing ]
-[ Grunts ]
[ Click. dial tone ]
[ Insects chirping ]
[ Down-tempo music plays ]
♪♪
[ Engine revs ]
[ Sirens wailing ]
[ Tires screeching ]
♪♪
[ Music builds ]
[ Blade slicing. man grunts ]
♪♪
[ Music builds ]
[ Gunshot echoes ]
[ Gunfire. bullets ricocheting ]
[ Down-tempo music plays ]
♪♪
[ Siren wailing ]
[ Gunshot echoes ]
[ Gunfire ]
♪♪
[ Music slows ]
[ Music builds ]
♪♪
[ No audio ]
[ Music slows ]
♪♪
[ Hammer thuds ]
[ Music builds ]
♪♪
[ Razor buzzing ]
-[ Grunting ]
♪♪
[ Shouting indistinctly ]
[ Muffled screaming ]
♪♪
[ Shotgun clicks ]
[ Music builds ]
♪♪
[ Music ends ]
[ Insects chirping.
vehicles passing in distance ]
[ Siren wailing in distance ]
[ Merrell Fankhauser's "Lila"
playing ]
-♪ Lila came the day
I heard it thunder ♪
-♪ Lila ♪
-♪ There she was.
just a-standing by herself ♪
♪♪
♪ When she came.
she brought me flowers ♪
♪ And. baby... ♪
♪♪
-[ Whistles ]
[ Gunshots. casings clattering ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
♪♪
[ Music builds ]
[ Paper shuffling ]
-[ Inhales sharply ]
[ Exhales deeply ]
♪♪
[ Wick hissing.
explosion echoes ]
[ Explosion. glass breaking ]
♪♪
[ Gunfire ]
[ Gunfire. bullets ricocheting ]
♪♪
-[ Grunting ]
[ Gunfire ]
♪♪
[ Gunshot echoes. man grunts ]
[ Gunshot echoes ]
♪♪
[ Blade slicing.
gunshot echoes ]
♪♪
[ Gunshots ]
-[ Grunting ]
-[ Grunts ]
-Oh!
♪♪
[ Gunshot ]
[ Gunfire continues ]
[ Music slows ]
♪♪
[ Gunfire in distance ]
[ Gunfire continues ]
♪♪
-[ Grunts ]
[ Engines rev. tires screech ]
[ Music slows ]
♪♪
[ Bell chimes ]
[ Both grunting ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
♪♪
-[ Screams ]
-[ Grunts ]
♪♪
-Oh! Fuck!
Oh!
[ Grunts ]
♪♪
[ Fist thudding ]
[ Music builds ]
[ Groaning ]
Aah!
-[ Grunting ]
♪♪
[ Both grunting ]
-Aah!
[ Grunting ]
♪♪
[ Music builds ]
[ Gunshot ]
-[ Grunts. groaning ]
[ Grunts. gasping ]
[ Exhales deeply.
breathing heavily ]
[ Bell chimes ]
[ Down-tempo music plays ]
♪♪
[ Music builds ]
-[ Grunting ]
♪♪
[ Engines revving ]
[ Tires screeching.
engine revving ]
[ Music builds ]
♪♪
[ Glass breaking.
tires screeching ]
[ Tires screeching.
engine revving ]
[ Gunshot echoes ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
♪♪
[ Engine starts. revs ]
[ Engine revving.
tires screeching ]
♪♪
-[ Grunting ]
[ Tires screeching ]
[ Down-tempo music plays ]
♪♪
[ Music builds ]
[ Engine cranking ]
♪♪
-Whoa.
[ Engine starts ]
♪♪
[ Tires screeching ]
-[ Grunting ]
♪♪
[ Engine revving ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Horn blares.
tires screeching ]
[ Gunshots echoing ]
♪♪
[ Blade slicing ]
-[ Screams ]
[ Horn blares ]
[ Tires screeching ]
-[ Grunting ]
♪♪
[ Horn blares ]
-[ Grunting. gasping ]
♪♪
[ Glass breaking.
metal screeching ]
[ Down-tempo music plays ]
♪♪
[ Groans ]
[ Grunts ]
♪♪
[ Metal creaking ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Music builds ]
♪♪
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Sirens wailing in distance ]
♪♪
[ Siren wailing ]
[ Music builds ]
♪♪
[ Birds chirping. cawing ]
[ Down-tempo music plays ]
♪♪
[ Tank rattling ]
[ Music builds ]
♪♪
[ Tank rattling ]
[ Clattering in distance ]
[ Footsteps approaching ]
♪♪
[ Air hissing ]
[ Valve squeaks. hissing stops ]
-[ Exhales deeply ]
♪♪
[ Breathing slowly ]
[ Music builds ]
♪♪
-I loved her.
I loved her.
♪♪
-I still do.
[ Gunshot echoes ]
[ Jack White's "Archbishop
Harold Holmes" plays ]
♪♪
-♪ Dear friend.
if you want to feel better ♪
♪ Don't let the devil
make you toss this letter ♪
♪ If you've been crossed up
by hoodoo-voodoo ♪
♪ A wizard or the lizard ♪
♪ If you got family trouble.
man trouble. woman trouble ♪
♪ No light through the tunnel ♪
♪ If you're looking for
a true friend or a true lover ♪
♪ Or if you've been living
undercover ♪
♪ Well. I'm coming to your town
to break it all down ♪
♪ And help you
with all of this ♪
♪ I'm looking to help you
find bliss one day or one way ♪
♪ Can't miss ♪
♪♪
♪ I'm here to tear all the walls
down ♪
♪ Doesn't matter if it's
a large town or a small town ♪
♪ Just like Joshua and
the fabled walls of Jericho ♪
♪ I'm here to tear down
the institution ♪
♪ God spoke to me.
said. "Listen to me ♪
♪ I anoint you with the power
that'll get 'em all movin'" ♪
♪ You're agitated.
you've prayed and meditated ♪
♪ You're concentrated
on getting elevated ♪
♪ By sundown Monday ♪
♪ You who come will be blessed
with a big money blessing ♪
♪ You will be doubted
by all the unbelievers ♪
♪ And all of the friends
I'm addressing ♪
♪ But you must tell
seven friends ♪
♪ You must first bring
♪ And don't be selfish
and keep this all to yourself ♪
♪ And don't eat shellfish ♪
♪ Hate is trying to take someone
else's love for yourself ♪
♪ But I'm here to tell you ♪
♪ That love is trying to help
someone else ♪
♪♪
♪ I realize that you have tried
and tried ♪
♪ And are just about ready
to give up ♪
♪ But I got good news for you ♪
♪ God has spoken to my mind
and told me to tell you ♪
♪ To get moving in the right
direction for a change ♪
♪ I'm gonna put you
in the fast lane! ♪
♪ You need to see me right away
so I can fix this-ah ♪
♪♪
♪ You need to see me
right away ♪
♪♪
♪ You need to see me right away
so I can fix this-ah ♪
♪♪
♪ You need to see me
right about now ♪
♪♪
♪ God of Seven. open up
the windows of heaven ♪
♪ And pour out a rich
and mighty blessing ♪
♪ Not on his town or her town.
but your town ♪
♪ Are you ready
for the message? ♪
♪ I have a special
financial blessing ♪
♪ That once I have placed
in your hand ♪
♪ Yeah. I want you to begin
using this blessing ♪
♪ On the very first day
that you can ♪
♪ And if you are suffering
a strange sickness-ah ♪
♪♪
♪ Or someone is blocking up
all of your success-ah ♪
♪ You need to see me right away
so I can fix this-ah ♪
♪♪
Signed sincerely. yours
in faith. love. and peace.
your friend Archbishop
Harold Holmes.
[ Down-tempo music plays ]
♪♪
[ Dramatic music plays ]